Women's Studies Oral History Project; Records ua600.006
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Women's Studies Oral History Collection
1997
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua600.006
0.17 cubic ft.
Consists of cassette recordings and transcriptions of interviews documenting the creation of the Women's Studies Program at the then State University of New York at Albany in the 1970's. The interviews were conducted, with one exception, by Judith Hudson, retiring University Libraries bibliographer for Women's Studies.
Access
Access to this collection is restricted because it is unprocessed. Portions of the collection may contain recent administrative records and/or personally identifiable information. Please contact an archivist for more information.
Acquisition Information
All items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Historical Note
The Women's Studies Program was created in 1972. It became the Department of Women's Studies in 1990. It is currently called the Department of Women's, Gender, and Sexuality Studies.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains 11 cassette recordings, transcripts of the recordings, and consent forms.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection is unprocessed and is likely disorganized. Individual items may be difficult to find.
Women; Oral history; Women's studies; oral histories (document genres); Transcripts; UAlbany Academic Departments; State University of New York at Albany
- Women's Studies Oral History Project Concent Forms, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Judith E. Barlow Interview, 1997 March 20 (Box 1, Cassette 1)
- Judith E. Barlow Interview Transcript, 1997 March 20 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Christine Bose Interview, 1997 March 11 (Box 1, Cassette 2)
- Christine Bose Interview Transcript, 1997 March 11 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Francine Frank Interview, 1997 April 3 (Box 1, Cassette 3)
- Francine Frank Interview Transcript, 1997 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Judith Hudson Interview, 1997 September 6 (Box 1, Cassette 4)
- Linda Nicholson Interview, 1997 April 7 (Box 1, Cassette 5)
- Linda Nicholson Interview Transcript, 1997 April 7 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Iris Berger Interview, 1997 April 8 (Box 1, Cassette 6)
- Iris Berger Interview Transcript, 1997 April 8 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Judith Fetterly Interview, 1997 April 10 (Box 1, Cassette 7)
- Judith Fetterly Interview Transcript, 1997 April 10 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- June Hahner Interview, 1997 April 17 (Box 1, Cassette 8)
- June Hahner Interview Transcript, 1997 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Bonnie Spanier Interview, 1997 April 23 (Box 1, Cassette 9)
- Bonnie Spanier Interview Transcript, 1997 April 23 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Glenna Spitze Interview, 1997 April 29 (Box 1, Cassette 10)
- Glenna Spitze Interview Transcript, 1997 April 29 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Joan Shultz Inteview, 1997 January 28 (Box 1, Cassette 11)
- Joan Shultz Inteview Transcript, 1997 January 28 (Box 1, Folder 11)